svgator.com 2019-02-17

# Privacy Policy | SVGator

  * It is SVGator's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. By providing your personal data to SVGator (by registering as a user and/or using the SVGator tool), you accept that your personal data will be used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we have developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our Privacy Policy below.
  * 1\. What information do we collect?
  * a) Basic account information
  * When registering on or using our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, title, email address, postal or other physical address, phone number, or other details. You give us this information voluntarily by creating an account and using our services.
  * If you log into SVGator with a social networking credential, such as with your Facebook or Google+ account, we will ask permission to access basic information from that account, such as your name and email address. The information we get from Facebook and Google+ depends on your settings and their privacy policies. You can stop sharing that information with us at any moment by removing SVGator’s access to that account. 
  * b) Technical information
  * We collect the following types of information when you access or use our Site, Software, and/or Services to securely and reliably set up and maintain your account and to provide our services to you:
    * Usage data
      * Sign-up data
      * Authentication detail
      * Login history
    * Session log and actions taken during a session
    * Device specific information (device type, identifiers, and events)
    * Ads engagement
      * Our ads served to a page and likelihood you have seen them
      * Actions on our ads
    * Cookies associated with your account
      * Verifying your login credentials
      * Remembering you across sessions and devices
  * c) Payment information
  * When you register for our paid services you might also provide payment information, such as billing address or payment card details, which we collect via secure payment processing services. We use third-party payment processors to process payments made to us. We do not retain any personally identifiable information or any financial information such as credit card numbers.
  * 2\. What do we do with the information we collect?
  * We may use and disclose your personal information only as follows:
    * To identify you when you use SVGator, to personalize your experience and process your transactions.
    * Send you payment and renewal confirmations.
    * To improve our website and offer new features.
    * To allow us to better service you in responding to your questions.
    * To protect the safety or integrity of our platform, including to help prevent spam, fraud, security, or technical issues.
    * To send periodic emails regarding services updates. Each time we send you marketing materials, we give you the option to unsubscribe.
  * 3\. How we share the information we collect?
  * We use trusted third party companies that meet high data protection and security standards to help us deliver, analyze, and improve our services (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, email communication, database management, web analytics such as Google Analytics and payment processing). 
  * These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf.
  * 4\. Protection of your information
  * Your privacy and the security of your personal information are important to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and as a result, we can not ensure the security of Information you transmit to us, including Personal Data and User Content; accordingly, you acknowledge that you do so at your own risk.
  * We also use industry-standard encryption (transport layer security (“TLS”) or secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology) to protect your data in transit. Encryption keeps your data private while in transit.
  * Once we receive your data, we protect it on our servers using security safeguards and reasonable measures to prevent the unauthorized disclosure or use of your data.
  * 5\. How you control the information we receive?
  * You have a right to be informed of personal data processed by SVGator, a right to rectification/correction, erasure, and restriction of processing. You can also edit information in your profile at any time, delete your billing method and billing address, link or unlink your SVGator account from other services like Facebook and Google.
  * To exercise any of the rights mentioned in this Privacy Policy and/or in case of questions you may email us at contact@svgator.com. We will get back to you within 30 days from the date of your email.
  * 6\. How long we keep your information?
  * We keep your information only so long as we need it to provide SVGator to you and fulfill the purposes described in this policy. When we no longer need to use your information and there is no need for us to keep it to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, we remove it from our systems.
  * 7\. Changing our Privacy Policy
  * If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Under appropriate circumstances, we may send you email notice of such changes, but we urge you not to rely on that method of receiving information.
  * Privacy Policy: Last Modified May 24, 2018 
  * Questions about our Privacy Policy should be sent to us at contact@svgator.com
    * Address:
    * Smartketer LLC
    * 156 2nd Street, San Francisco, CA 94105 USA
    * (001) 650-741-1328
